

MOHIT KUMAR

Generative Al Engineer

C

+91-9466338524



mohitdcsa@gmail.com



<u>LinkedIn</u>



<u>GitHub</u>

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Applications 🖸

Maharshi Dayanand University Rohtak 2022 - 2024

Bachelor of Science 🖸

Indira Gandhi University Meerpur Rewari 2018 - 2021

SKILLS

- Generative Al
- Prompt Engineering
- RAG, Vector DB
- LangChain, LlamaIndex
- Model Evaluation
- · Python, Gradio
- HTML, CSS, UX UI

CERTIFICATIONS

ChatGPT Prompt ☐ Engineering for Developers

Issuing Authority : DeepLearning.Al Completion Date: June 23, 2024

- User-Centered Design: Creating precise prompts for effective AI interactions.
- Prototyping and Testing:
 Enhancing Al-driven
 conversations through prompt
 optimization and testing.

Foundation of UX Design $\, \, \underline{\ } \,$

Issuing Authority : Amanda Brophy Global Completion Date: Oct 8, 2023

- **User-Centered Design:** Creating intuitive, user-focused designs.
- Prototyping and Testing: Building wireframes and conducting usability tests.

PROFILE SUMMARY

As a Generative AI Engineer, I create digital experiences that blend aesthetics and functionality. My user-centered, intuitive, and visually appealing designs captivate users and solve their problems efficiently. I leverage generative AI technologies to make technology accessible and enjoyable, driving user satisfaction and business success.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Edquest

May 2024 - Present

Jan 2024 - May 2024

Generative AI Engineer

- Al Integration: Developed and implemented Al-powered solutions for projects.
- Research & Development: Conducted in-depth research to innovate and enhance technology applications.

Indian Institute of Technology New Delhi

UX UI Design Intern

- · Crafted intuitive and aesthetically pleasing interfaces that prioritize UX and engagement.
- Designed user-centered workflows and visuals to optimize usability and satisfaction across digital platforms

PROJECTS

Invoice data extraction [7]

Jun 2024 - Jul 2024

Gen Al, Gradio, Python, Prompt Engineering

- Automating data extraction with Al-powered sys. For accurate and efficient processing.
- Extracting key details in JSON to streamline financial workflows and ensure compliance.

Burger Bot 🖸

Jan 2024- May 2024

Gen Al, Gradio, Python, Prompt Engineering

- Transform food ordering with generative AI, personalized and dynamic interactions.
- Real-time processing, intuitive, personalized recommendations, efficient and engaging.

Travel Bot 🖸

Mar 2024- Jun 2024

Gen Al, Gradio, Python, Prompt Engineering

- Simplify trips with personalized recommendations and seamless, integrated services.
- Efficient User Interface: Real-time updates, custom itineraries, intuitive navigation.

Vigilant Vision 🖸

Feb 2024 - May 2024

Al-powered object detection

- Vigilance Vision enhances security with Al-powered object detection.
- Detecting adult content in CCTV ensures safety and compliance.

MyJob Portal 🖸

Mar 2022- Jun 2022

JSP Project

- Global jobseekers can register, apply, and complete online assessments.
- Seamlessly connects candidates and employers, streamlining the recruitment process.